tikitoro
Skincare is equal
parts art
and science.
But the trick to caring for
your skin is knowing your skin type.
What skin type does your youngster have?
It is crucia l to understand this to be a ble to provide skin-nurturing specific to his or her needs.
Dry Skin
Dry skin looks flaky and dull. It is
"often caused by extreme weather conditions such as cold; usage of harsh chemicals that dry up skin cells; or low production of sebum. Needs to be well-moisturised through the year. (Yes, even teens"
may have dry skin.)
Sensitive skin
Sensitive skin is prone to
"inflammation and may appear red and irritated. Sensitive skin may react to a host of elements, even natural ones. Synthetic ingredients,harsh chemicals are a complete no-no; even strong"
perfumes are best avoided.
Oily skin
If the T-zone (forehead and down
"the nose) is excessively greasy upon waking, it indicates oily skin.Also,if your teen's face gets visibly oily injust a few hours, it indicates excess sebum (the oily, waxy substance) which may clog"
pores and trigger acne.
Normal Skin
"Normal skin is well-balanced,feels"
"soft and is never too oily or dry. Lucky ones with such problem-free skin seldom suffer breakouts or patchy dry skin.However, remember to"
emphasise to your teen that he or she must have a skincare routine. Follow
the basics and you're good to go.
Combination skin
Itcan be a combination of any of
"the skin types and may change according to the season. Usually, combination skin tends to be oily at the forehead and the T-zone, and dry at the cheeks. Some parts of it feel like it's oozing sebum while"
others are not!
Why choose Tikitoro for your youngster?
"It's the first-of-a-kind, vegan formulation created especially for the tender developing skin of children between ages 4-10 and 11-16."
tikitoro
tikitoro                     l-'1::!ro1l'lq
body lotion
"°''*......,""""""'""""JM<.....i...sti.."
"...li..H;<W'>ll--.\•-t""""I"
tikitoro
"sh'""a""""m""'""""p'''""o•o"
tikitoro
"re'u.:li•""'9"
face wash
The best part?
It is the perfect fit for ALL skin types.
Take a picture with Tikitoro and Ill.on your next purchase.
OFF
Simply upload a piclure of your Tikiloro producls on your
instagram feed & tag us (@tikitoroindia). Don't forget to tell
us what you think. We'd love a review!
Follow us on
w w w .t i k i t o r o .c o m
